Tim Hoyt

231 Elkwood Ave. Imperial Beach, CA 91932 (619) 994-4853

Personal trainer, group fitness instructor, construction project administrator, and Chief Technology Officer. Keen ability to work with the general public in both group and private setting and effectively communicating instruction for results. Experienced with coordination, planning, and organization of commercial/industrial construction projects. Also, adapt in creating new software/hardware protocols for unattended kiosks for mass deployment projects.

Education/Certifications/Skills:

IndoRow Water Rowing and Shockwave Instructor Certification 2012-Current

Bachelor's Degree in Political Science, San Diego State University: 2010

National Exercise & Sports Trainers Association Personal Trainer Certification (NESTA):

2007-Current

Schwinn Indoor Cycle Instructor Certification: September 2010-Current

IDEA Fitness Conference 2010 - Classes Attended:

IndoRow: Indoor water rowing with Josh Crosby and Jay Blahnik

TRX Group Suspension Training Instructor Certification: 2011-Current

Boy Scouts of America, Eagle Scout: 2005

Experience:

Chief Technology Officer: December 2018-Present Smart Beverage Technologies, LLC 2820 Via Orange Way, Suite O Spring Valley, CA 91978 (877) 333-9494 www.smartbeverage.tech

- Create and Manage new UX/UI solutions to improve customer experience
- Evaluate new technology for deployment in an unattended environment

- Manage all credit card processing and integration of new POS (point-of-sale) systems
- Oversee all hardware production and inventory

Office Administrator/Sales Rep/Logistics/General Operations: November 2012-Dec. 2018 Vendture LLC., DBA Eatwave 1510 Front St., Ste. 100 San Diego, CA 92101 (619) 908-1181

- Organize and initiate sales initiatives
- Generate databases and internal documents for company management and operations.
- Meet with prospective clients and execute sales contracts
- Manage all product inventory, shipping and receiving logistics

Office Administrator/Sales Coordinator/Field Supervisor/Project Coordinator: June 2009-Nov. 2012 Air Management Systems/Southwestern Solar Systems 9302 Bond Ave, El Cajon, CA 92021 (619) 390-7803/ (619) 334-3149

www.airmanagementsystems.com/www.southwesternsolarsystems.com

- Disseminate information such as regulations and safety to other employees, personal, i.e., guidance, direction and support to other employees.
- Generate construction plans, schedules, assure materials are ordered, and assure all work is performed in a professional manner.
- Coordinate and maintain all sales and product inventories, making sure that all employees follow the correct procedures relating to the jobs and materials.
- Organize and execute all new projects to ensure that the job is profitable.

Owner/Personal Trainer/Group Fitness Instructor: April 2010-Present C3 Fitness
2471 Jamacha Rd, El Cajon, CA 92019
(619) 517-7980
www.c3fitnessstudio.com

• Promote professionalism within the workplace and work with gym members and employees to make them feel comfortable within the facility.

- Support clients and other trainers in making the facility operate as efficiently as possible
- Identify issues and solve problems when clients/members come to me with frustration regarding fitness or their workouts.
- Teach and deliver fitness techniques to groups and individuals in the facility as well as through outdoor boot camp style workouts. I design plans for clients to reach their fitness goals, whether it be weight loss, muscle gain, etc.

Personal Trainer/Group Fitness Instructor: January 2007- October 2009 Glaze Fitness Inc. 851 Jamacha Rd, El Cajon, CA 92019 (619)588-7300 www.GlazeFitness.com

- Certified Personal Fitness Trainer develop personalized fitness programs for all age groups and provide grouping personal training
- Glaze Fitness Boot Camp instructing groups of 20-30 adult individuals

ATM Technician: June 2006-June 2008 Card Direct Elite 30045 Mickelson Way, Murrieta, CA, 92563 (951) 304-0825

 ATM Service Technician – support ATM machines "in the field" and work with customers to resolve technical problems

Legal Assistant: January 2005-May 2006 Hoyt Law Firm 181 Rea Ave, El Cajon, CA 92020 (619) 588-1726 www.hoytlawfirm.org

• Performed filing, copying, data entry, answering phones, and legal research documentation; understand San Diego Court Filing Systems